http://www.allanimation.com/pages/privacy-policy

Marvel Fine Art - Official Online Store!
Search
Marvel Fine Art - Official Online Store!
JIM LEE
JOHN ROMITA SR.
Privacy Policy
You are protected. Here’s how.
- HOW AND WHEN WE COLLECT INFORMATION
We collect "personal" information from you when you provide it to us. For example, if you purchase artwork from us, we may collect your name, mailing address and telephone number. If you sign up to receive a newsletter, we will collect your email address. If you take advantage of special services offered by us, we may collect other personal information about you.
- WHAT WE DO WITH THAT INFO
The Choice Group protects your privacy. Under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share your e-mail address with any other company for their marketing purposes. We use your personal information for internal purposes such as processing and keeping you informed of your order. You may, from time to time, receive information from us about new features, new services and special offers we think you'll find valuable.The personal information that you give us when you place an order is used to process and fulfill your order. We also use your personal information for our own internal purposes, such as providing customer support or providing, maintaining, evaluating and improving our products and services.
- We partner with one or more credit card processing companies to assist us in processing your payment. However, those companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
- We may disclose the personal and non-personal information of our customers to any successor-in-interest of ours, such as a company that acquires our business. We may need to disclose your personal information when required by law or when we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process.
- WE MAY LINK TO OTHER SITES IF THEY ARE COOL.
The Choice Group website may contain links to web sites operated by other companies. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of such other websites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our website.
- IP ADDRESS
We also collect "non-personal" information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous web site you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your IP address. "Non-personal" information cannot be easily used to personally identify you. We may use your non-personal information to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your non-personal information may also be used to gather broad demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns and website usage. This information aids us in developing the design and layout of the website to give our users the best web experience possible.
- GOOGLE ADWORDS, COOKIES & REMARKETING
In addition, like almost all e-commerce web sites, we use "cookies." Cookies are bits of information that are stored on your computer by your web browser. Although our cookies don't store any of your personal information, they do allow us to do things like keep items in your shopping cart between visits or during the same visit or provide you with a more personalized user experience. Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. If you haven't changed your computer's settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies.
This website also uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to this website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
- UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us from unauthorized access or disclosure, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or other acts or omissions.
- UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION
If your personal information changes, you may correct, update or remove personal information previously provided to us by contacting our customer service department at Support@ChoiceCollect.com
- CONTACT US
If you ever have any questions regarding our privacy policy please contact us at Support@ChoiceCollect.com
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
